Finding Aid for the In the Life records LSC.2178
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Legal Records, (1992-2012)
  - ITL ITLM Licensor, 2005, 2010 (Box 32)
    Correspondence and agreements for music licensing. Removed from binder for preservation purposes.
  - ITL Legal, 1994-1995 (Box 36)
    Memo re: ITL program rights for a small number of episodes. Show 402 talent agreement with Greg Watt; work-for-hire agreement with John Catania.
  - ITL License agreement and release, 2010 (Box 32)
    Correspondence and episode agreement for episode 1901; materials release for episode 1904
  - ITL Releases, 2011-2012 (Box 36)
    Materials, location, and appurtenance release agreements for ITL episodes.
  - ITL season XIX license agreement with educational broadcasting corporation (WNET), 2009 Dec (Box 22)
  - ITL Talent, 1994 (Box 36)
    Talent agreements.
  - ITL Web Exclusive, 2009-2012 (Box 32)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Appearance and materials releases for use in ITL web exclusive.
  - Jean Carlomusto & Licenses, ca. 2006 (Box 33)
    License agreements.
  - Legal Contracts, 1992-1994 (Box 36)
    Talent, appearance release, and work-for-hire agreements for ITL.
  - Legal Documents - Releases, 1992-1993 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous Appearance Releases, 2001 (Box 33)
    List of agreements obtained and needed for ITL episodes.
  - Morgan's - do not remove, 1992, 1995, 1999 (Box 67)
    Correspondence from VLA (Volunteer Lawyers for the Arts); correspondence frame ITL re: corporate sponsorships, waivers and release forms.
  - Online partner contracts (2 folders), 1999-2001 (Box 63)
    License agreements between ITL and Online Partners, for ITL clips.
  - PrideVision Agreement (3 folders), 2001-2002 (Box 67)
    License agreements and email correspondence.
  - Sara Cytron, 1992, 1993 (Box 33)
    Talent agreement, biography, and script for Sara Cytron.
  - Sisters of Perpetual Indulgence, 2008 (Box 36)
    Correspondence, work-for-hire agreement, and story pitch for ITL segment.
  - Wolfe Video, ca. 1994-2003 (Box 48)
    Distribution agreement, invoices.
  - Work For Hire agreements, 1992, 1994 (Box 37)
    Work-for-hire agreements
- Executive Director's Files, (1992-2012, undated)
  The Executive Director's Files include materials such as annual budgets, strategic plans, company history, staff and board meeting minutes, contracts, licensing agreements, copyright information, and reports from various internal departments and external consultants. There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  - 20th Anniversary, 2012 (Box 5)
  - Allens Arthur Robinson, 2007-2008 (Box 11)
  - American Program Service, ca. 1995-2001 (Box 11)
  - American Psychiatric Association, 2001 (Box 11)
  - American Public Television, 1999-2000, 2004 (Box 9)
  - American Public Television /Educational Broadcasting Corporation1900 series agreement, 2009 (Box 9)
  - Annual Budget 92-93 1st season, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - Annual Budget 93-94 2nd season, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - Annual survey 2002 (Box 8)
  - Archive File from Jane Hoffman, ca. 1997-2005 (Box 9)
  - Archives, ca. 2006-2009 (Box 6)
    Notes and email correspondence referencing ITL archival project.
  - Awards, 1998 (Box 11)
  - BBB wise giving (2 folders), 2006-2010 (Box 6)
  - Big Think, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Blame Canada, 2001-2003 (Box 10)
  - Board Development Committee (2 folders), 2002-2003; 2005 (Box 8)
  - Board Pledges (Old), ca. 1999-2001 (Box 8)
    Fundraising and donor information.
  - Boys... Manchester, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Brand Identity workshop, 2006 Nov 11 (Box 3)
  - Brand survey, 2006-2007 (Box 3)
  - Branding, ca. 2006-2009 (Box 3)
  - Brian's weekly staff meeting notes, 2010-2011 (Box 6)
  - Budget FY00, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY01, 2001 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY02, 2002 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY07, 2007 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY08, 2008 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY09, 2009 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY10, 2010 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY11, 2011 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY95, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY96, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Budget FY97, 1997 (Box 8)
  - C1TV license agreement, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Channel 13 - 1200 series contract, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Channel Thirteen (13) - 1600 series contract, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Channel Thirteen (13) - 1700 series contract, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Channel Thirteen (13) - Educational Broadcasting Corporation 1800 series contract, 2008 (Box 9)
  - Channel Thirteen (13) - Educational Broadcasting Corporation 990, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Channel Thirteen (13) - Info, 2005, 2009 (Box 9)
  - Channel Thirteen (13) Agreement - 1100 revised, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Channel Thirteen (13) contract - 1400 series, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Channel Thirteen (13) contract - 1500 series, ca. 2001-2005 (Box 10)
  - Chip's weekly staff meeting notes, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Christian's meeting notes, 2008-2009 (Box 2)
  - Chuy's weekly staff meeting notes, 2011-2012 (Box 6)
  - Cinema Guild (The), 2003-2004 (Box 11)
  - Communications, 2009-2011 (Box 6)
  - Consulting Proposal 2006 (Box 3)
  - Copyright Info - Logo, ca. 2006 (Box 7)
    Copyright forms for ITL "Encore" episodes for Logo network.
  - Dev Committee Meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 8)
  - Distribution, undated (Box 6)
    Board meeting notes, articles.
  - Editorial Board 06/08 - 06/10, 2008 June-June 2010 (Box 5)
  - Education = Action, ca. 2002 (Box 1)
  - Educational Home Video, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Emmy award, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Erik's weekly staff meeting notes, 2008-2012 (Box 6)
  - Executive Director retreat, ca. 2007-2010 (Box 5)
  - Executive Director support group, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Executive Director's Report 9/12, 2012 Sep (Box 7)
  - Foundations/Membership, 1998-1999 (Box 11)
  - Fundraising materials, 1995-1998 (Box 1)
    Correspondence.
  - FY04 1300 series contract - PBS contract, 2004 (Box 10)
  - FY12 Marketing and Communications manual, 2012 (Box 3)
  - FY12 Staff meetings, 2012 (Box 4)
  - Gala 2009 (Box 7)
  - Gala 2010 (Box 7)
  - Gala 2011 (Box 7)
  - Gay Satellite Television, 2008 (Box 11)
  - Harvey Fierstein, 2002-2004 (Box 11)
    Transcripts for Harvey Fierstein's Out Takes segment on In the Life.
  - Hate Mail, ca. 1992-1993 (Box 9)
  - Henry photographs, ca. 2000-2003 (Box 1)
  - Here Media, 2011-2012 (Box 6)
  - Historical narrative, undated (Box 5)
  - In the Life Media Catalyst Committee Meeting, 2008-2009 (Box 5)
  - In the Life: Raising a Community's Voice campaign (Box 8)
  - ITL Bulletins (2 folders), 1996-2007 (Box 2)
  - ITL history - staff, undated (Box 5)
  - ITL organizational history (Box 5)
    Organization analysis and recommendations.
  - Jayne, 2012 Aug 24 (Box 7)
  - Job descriptions, ca. 2004-2007 (Box 5)
  - Johnson & Johnson, 2008 (Box 8)
  - L.A. - panels, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Legal matters, 1996; 2009-2012 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Michelle Kristel to NYS re: amended tax reports 2004, 2005, 2006, 2007 (Box 63)
  - License Agreement - Channel Thirteen (13), 2001, 2002 (Box 10)
  - License issue - Take the A Train, 2001, 2008 (Box 11)
  - Life Circle, 2003-2005 (Box 8)
    ITL "Life Circle" membership and donor information.
  - Logo network, 2006 (Box 10)
  - Logo network, undated (Box 1)
    Marketing partnership information for Logo cable network.
  - Logo signed agreement, 2006 (Box 10)
  - Love Mail, ca. 1992-1993 (Box 9)
  - MAC AIDS, undated (Box 6)
    Notes and talking points for M.A.C AIDS Fund.
  - Management Team FY11, 2011 (Box 5)
  - Master Narrative (Box 1)
  - Member survey 1998 (Box 8)
  - Member survey 1999 (Box 8)
  - Member survey 2001 (Box 8)
  - Membership letters, 1993-1995, 2005 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous ED files, 2009-2012 (Box 6)
  - Morgan Greenwald's Board Notebook, ca. 1995-2004 (Box 1)
    Program information, policies, fundraising, legal materials, and board info.
  - Movement Advance Project, ca. 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Movies Unlimited, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Museum of Television and Radio, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Mygayweb.com, 2003 (Box 11)
  - National Advisory Council, 2009 (Box 7)
  - National Advisory Council, ca. 2001 (Box 1)
  - Network For Good (Box 1)
  - Oct 2008 binder: ITLM Catalyst Committee Strategy Session (Box 1)
  - Old ITL Mailings (Box 2)
  - Outreach Plan, 2007 (Box 7)
  - Palm Springs Pride, 2011-2012 (Box 6)
  - Personnel Handbook, 2011 (Box 5)
  - Photographs (Box 1)
    With images of David Martin, Joanna Grove, and Virginia Apuzzo.
  - Pride 2011 (Box 7)
  - PrideVision contract, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Pridevision contract and invoices, ca. 2002-2006 (Box 10)
  - Production - programming committee, ca. 2007-2011 (Box 7)
  - Ratings info, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Real Change, 2007 (Box 5)
  - Revenue information, 2012 (Box 3)
  - Ron's weekly meeting notes, 2008-2009 (Box 3)
  - Scott's weekly meeting notes, 2008-2009 (Box 2)
  - Senior staff/staff FY08, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Show history (Box 5)
    ITL programming proposals and list of individuals appearing on ITL.
  - Staff meeting minutes 92-03, 1992-2003 (Box 4)
  - Staff meetings 8/95-4/00, 1995 Aug-Apr 2000 (Box 4)
  - Staff meetings FY10, 2010 (Box 4)
  - Staff Meetings FY11, 2011 (Box 5)
  - Staff/management team FY09, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Plan, 2009-2012 (Box 3)
  - Strategic Plan - original 1999-2001, 1999-2001; 2002-2004 (Box 3)
  - Strategic Planning (2 folders), ca.1999-2008 (Box 1)
  - Supporting youth study guide, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Talking Points, 2006-2007 (Box 7)
  - Task Force, 2012 (Box 4)
  - Testimonials, ca. 2000-2008 (Box 8)
  - Timeline/Plan, 2012-2013 (Box 7)
  - Trademark information, 1996-1997, 2003-2009 (Box 11)
  - VideoFlicks.com, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Website (Box 1)
  - Weekly staff meeting notes, 2010-2011 (Box 2)
  - White House, 2010 (Box 6)
    Message to ITL from President Barack Obama (signature is not original).
  - Wolfe Video distribution agreement, 1994 (Box 11)
- Board of Directors Records, (1990-2012, undated)
  The Board of Directors Records series includes By-laws, meeting minutes, committee reports, and budgets representing the In the Life Board of Directors and its various committees. There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  - Board member resumes (2 folders), ca. 1995-2000 (Box 63)
    Past and prospective resumes.
  - Board members retired, 1998 (Box 63)
    Board member contact list and correspondence.
  - Board Notes and Board Meeting Notes (19 folders), 2007-2008; 2010-2012 (Box 20)
  - Board Notes and Board Meeting Notes (27 folders), 2003-2007; 2011, 2012 (Box 18)
  - Board Notes and Board Meeting Notes (29 folders), 1995-1999; 2000-2003; 2008-2011 (Box 19)
  - Board Notes and Board Meeting Notes (3 folders), 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Board Notes and Board Meeting Notes (6 folders), 2005, 2012 (Box 17)
  - Board referral forms, undated (Box 63)
  - Copies of the Audited Financials (Audited Financial Statements) (8 items), 2011 June-June 2003 (Box 21)
  - Fiscal Management Assessment, 2007 (Box 21)
  - Organizational Studies, 2006 (Box 21)
  - Ruth Messinger letter to Tom Morgan re: support for John Scagliotti's proposal In the Life (photocopy), 1990 Nov 26 (Box 67)
    Regarding support for starting ITL television program.
  - Strategic Plan (2 folders), 2001-2004; 2009-2012 (Box 21)
- Publicity and Press materials, (1991-2012; undated)
  Publicity and Press Materials consist of clippings, press kits, newsletters, publicity stills. The bulk of the clippings represent write-ups about ITL. Additionally there are a lesser amount of clippings documenting LGBT-related films, television programming, theatre productions, and exhibits, some of which may have been used as potential story ideas for ITL segments, such as Real to Reel and In the States. The series may contain duplicates of materials found in the Production Records series, such as episode guides and publicity stills. There is no specific arrangement to this series.
  - 10th Anniversary of IN THE LIFE press kit, 2002 (Box 45)
    Press kit.
  - 1998 Gay Press Report (Box 51)
  - 2002 Lambda Liberty Award (Box 45)
    ITL press release referencing award received by ITL.
  - A Knock Out, 2004 (Box 55)
    Press release for documentary film.
  - Articles (2 folders), ca. 1990s (Box 64)
    Clippings referencing ITL, with small number of articles re: LGBT issues.
  - Articles and publications, ca. 2002- 2012 (Box 69)
    Materials reference ITL, or LGBT community.
  - Cinema Guild (The), 2001 (Box 53)
  - Communications Assistant - magazines, ca. 2006-2012 (Box 68)
    LGBT Magazines.
  - Dance Manhattan, 2004 (Box 53)
  - Embalmer (The), 2003 (Box 53)
  - Emmy's, 1999-2000 (Box 48)
    Press and related material regarding ITL's Emmy nomination.
  - Emmy's 2000 program (Box 67)
  - Falco Ink., 2004 June 24 (Box 53)
  - Fish Can't Fly, 2005 (Box 53)
    Press kit for documentary film.
  - Ford Foundation, 2002 (Box 45)
    ITL press release referencing grant awarded by Ford Foundation.
  - Gay Pioneers, 2004 (Box 55)
    Press kit for documentary program.
  - Germany, 1997 (Box 53)
    Brochures, articles, and exhibition catalog referencing exhibit at Goethe-Institut.
  - Get Bruce, 1999 (Box 55)
    Publicity stills and slides for film.
  - Graham Norton Effect, 2004 (Box 55)
    Press kit for television program.
  - Harry Hay (The) Documentary Project, 2001 (Box 55)
    Press kit for documentary film. Includes correspondence regarding potential use on ITL.
  - Holding Tank, 2003 (Box 53)
    Brochure for rental space.
  - How Do I Look?, 2002-2004 (Box 55)
  - I Am My Own Husband?, undated (Box 55)
    Press release for play.
  - I Cant Marry You, 2003 (Box 55)
  - I Look Up To The Sky Now, 2003 (Box 55)
    Press kit (with DVD) for documentary film.
  - In My Father's Church, 2004 (Box 55)
    Press release for film.
  - In the Life program guides, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box 63)
  - International Fringe Festival, 2004 (Box 55)
    Press releases.
  - Iris, 2001 (Box 55)
    Press kit for film.
  - ITL 906/704 episode photographs, 2000 (Box 45)
    Publicity stills for episodes.
  - ITL advertising, news clippings, photographs, ca. 1999-2004 (Box 65)
    ITL brochures, press, and proof sheets.
  - ITL Anniversary Video 5th Season, 1997 (Box 44)
    Publicity stills.
  - ITL articles, ca. 1998-2005 (Box 49)
    Clippings referencing ITL.
  - ITL articles, ca. 2002-2003 (Box 48)
  - ITL articles, ca. 1998-2002 (Box 67)
    ITL fact sheets, articles referencing ITL, and Gay Press Report.
  - ITL articles (3 folders), 1995-1999 (Box 63)
    Articles referencing ITL, from New York Times, Los Angeles Times, TV Guide, Chicago Tribune, among others.
  - ITL clippings - Outlines magazine, 1994-1998 (Box 63)
  - ITL Clippings (9 folders), 1993-1999, 2001-2003 (Box 64)
    Clippings referencing ITL
  - ITL Clippings, photographs, and special events ephemera (2 folders), ca.1990s-2002 (Box 65)
    ITL newsletters, press releases, broadcast guides, and clippings. Small amount of ITL publicity stills and press related to ITL Academy Award screening event.
  - ITL episode 1001-1012 -publicity stills and/or press releases (12 folders), 2000 Oct-Sep 2001 (Box 45)
    Press releases and publicity stills for episodes.
  - ITL episode 1101-1106 -publicity stills and/or press releases (6 folders), 2001 Oct-Mar 2002 (Box 45)
  - ITL episode 1107-1110 publicity stills and/or press releases (4 folders), 2002 Apr-July 2002 (Box 46)
    Press releases and publicity stills for episodes. Folder for episode 1108 contains press release only.
  - ITL episode 300-309 -publicity stills and press releases (13 folders), ca. 1990s (Box 43)
    With proof sheets and negatives
  - ITL episode 400-404 -publicity stills and press releases (4 folders), ca. 1995 (Box 44)
    With negatives. Folder for episode 400 contains press release only.
  - ITL episode 501-505 -publicity stills and press releases (9 folders), ca. 1996 (Box 44)
    With negatives. Folders for episodes 502, 503, and 505 contain press releases only.
  - ITL episode 600-606 -publicity stills and press releases (12 folders), 1996-1997 (Box 44)
    Folder for episode 600 contains press release only.
  - ITL episode 701-706 -publicity stills and press releases (10 folders), 1997-1998 (Box 44)
    With negatives. Folder for episode 704 contains press release only.
  - ITL episode 801-806 -publicity stills and press releases (8 folders), ca. 1998-1999 (Box 44)
    With negatives and slides. Folders for episodes 802, 803 contain press releases only.
  - ITL episode 901-905 -publicity stills and/or press releases (7 folders), 1999-2000 (Box 45)
    With negatives and slides. Folder for episode 901 contains press release only.
  - ITL episodes 201-207 - publicity stills (7 folders), ca. 1990s (Box 43)
    Photographs, negatives, and proof sheets
  - ITL Impact Sheets (5 items) (Box 48)
    Publicity sheet with facts about ITL's impact.
  - ITL Media Hits 1991-1994 (Box 39)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Clippings related to ITL.
  - ITL Media Hits 1997-1998 (Box 57)
    Clippings referencing ITL. Removed from binder for preservation purposes
  - ITL Media Hits 1999 (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - ITL Media Hits 2000-2002 (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - ITL Media Hits 2002-2003 (Box 48)
  - ITL Media Hits 2006 (Box 47)
  - ITL Media Hits 2007-2009 (2 folders) (Box 38)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Clippings related to ITL and general clippings related to LGBT issues.
  - ITL Media Hits from 1995-1999 (Box 39)
  - ITL Media Kit, undated (Box 50)
  - ITL National Broadcast schedule, 2002 Sep-Dec, 2003 Feb-Mar, 2006 May (Box 67)
  - ITL News Articles, ca. 1992-2002 (Box 48)
  - ITL News Articles, ca. 1997-2000 (Box 50)
  - ITL Newsletters, ca. 1992-2009 (Box 48)
  - ITL Newsletters & Broadcast schedule, 1998-2001 (Box 50)
  - ITL newsletters and guides: episodes 200-606 (2 folders), ca. 1992-1997 (Box 51)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. ITL newsletters and program guides relating to ITL episodes 200-606. With small amount of publicity stills.
  - ITL newsletters and guides: episodes 700-1012 (2 folders), ca. 1997-2001 (Box 52)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. ITL newsletters and program guides relating to ITL episodes 700-1012. With small amount of publicity stills.
  - ITL Newsletters/National Broadcast Schedule (1 of 2), ca. 2001-2008 (Box 52)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. ITL newsletters, broadcast guides, and schedules.
  - ITL Newsletters/National Broadcast Schedule (2 of 2), ca. 2001-2008 (Box 53)
  - ITL Pilot photographs (Box 43)
    With proof sheets and small amount of negatives
  - ITL Pilot press coverage June 92, 1992 (Box 64)
  - ITL presentation photographs, ca. 1990s-2000s (Box 45)
    Publicity photographs for various episodes.
  - ITL Press kit (outdated), ca. 2000 (Box 50)
  - ITL Press Kit Masters, ca. 1999-2001 (Box 59)
    ITL Press release text and small amount of articles about ITL.
  - ITL Press packets, ca. 1997-1998 (Box 64)
    With small number of articles referencing ITL.
  - ITL Press releases, 1995-1996 (Box 63)
  - ITL Press releases and articles, ca. 1992-2000 (Box 63)
  - ITL Press Releases for Episodes 300-304, ca. 1994-1995 (Box 38)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. With small amount of negatives. Press releases and publicity brochures for episodes.
  - ITL Publicity, 1992-1993 (Box 64)
    Press releases, articles, correspondence, mailing lists.
  - ITL publicity and press material - Metrosource 2001, ca. 1993-2003 (Box 39)
    Clippings related to ITL.
  - ITL publicity photographs, 1996 (Box 63)
    Photocopies of publicity stills, video box cover, and notes.
  - ITL Short Film and Video Awards Competition 1998 (Box 44)
    Press release for third annual competition.
  - ITL Viewer Mail - press release material, 1993-1994 (Box 48)
  - Jack, 2004 (Box 53)
    Press kit (with DVD) for Showtime original film.
  - Jamaica, 2004 (Box 53)
    Articles referencing homophobia in Jamaica.
  - Julie Johnson, 2001 (Box 55)
    Publicity still for film.
  - Kansas, 2003-2004 (Box 53)
    Promotional literature and map referencing the state of Kansas. Possible reference materials for ITL's "In the States" segment.
  - Katherine Linton photographs, ca. 1998 (Box 51)
    Publicity stills and headshots of ITL host, Katherine Linton. With slides, negatives, and proof sheets.
  - Kinsey Sicks, ca. 2001-2003 (Box 53)
    Articles and correspondence regarding drag singing group. Correspondence references potential inclusion of Kinsey Sicks on ITL.
  - Lady In Question Is Charles Busch (The), 2005 (Box 54)
  - Laramie Project, ca. 2001-2002 (Box 55)
    Press kit for HBO film, with small amount of slides.
  - Liberty: 3 Stories, 2003-2004 (Box 54)
    Press kit for documentary film, with correspondence suggesting its use in ITL segment, "Real to Reel."
  - Love! Valour! Compassion!, ca. 1993-1997 (Box 54)
    Articles, production notes, publicity stills and slides referencing film and director.
  - Madame Butterfly, 1993 (Box 54)
    Publicity stills for film.
  - Mailing archives/Press Materials (2 folders), ca. 1990-2006 (Box 52)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Samples of ITL membership mailings, ITL newsletters, membership guides
  - Milk, 2008 (Box 37)
    Press release and clippings for film.
  - Montana, 2004-2005 (Box 53)
    Vacation guide for Montana. Possible reference materials for ITL's "In the States" segment.
  - MTV/Showtime, 2002 (Box 51)
    Articles, notes, and correspondence regarding collaboration between MTV and Showtime to create cable channel for gay viewers.
  - National Film Board of Canada, ca. 2002 (Box 54)
    Film and video catalog and related brochures.
  - New Leadership, New Look Release, 2002 (Box 45)
    ITL press release.
  - New Orleans - Hurricane Katrina, 2005 (Box 53)
    Articles referencing effects of Hurricane Katrina on gay community.
  - Noah's Arc, ca. 2004 (Box 54)
    Articles and press information sheet for television series.
  - On The Couch, 2004 (Box 54)
  - One Nation Under God, 1993 (Box 54)
  - Out Of The Past, undated (Box 54)
    Teachers' guide for LGBT history.
  - Outlet Gay and Lesbian Entertainment Network memo (Viacom/Showtime) (Box 48)
  - Paternal Instinct, 2004 (Box 54)
    Press kit and correspondence regarding Cinemax original documentary film.
  - PBS - Distribution & Funding Guide for Independent Producers, undated (Box 54)
  - Phantom Audio, undated (Box 55)
    Press materials relating to rental space/locations.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 21)
    Publicity stills and head shots.
  - Photographs from early ITL episodes, ca. 1990s (Box 63)
    Publicity stills, proof sheets.
  - Positive Images - ITL facts, undated (Box 46)
    ITL press releases.
  - Postcards From Buster, 2005 (Box 54)
    Correspondence and articles regarding PBS children's television program.
  - Pressure, ca. 2002 (Box 55)
    Press materials relating to event rental space/locations.
  - PrideVision TV & Beyond!, ca. 1998-2001 (Box 54)
    New Video press kit with articles and correspondence regarding potential distribution for ITL.
  - Publicity stills for Joan Rivers and Roseanne Barr, 1992, undated (Box 67)
    All stills are signed.
  - Punks The Movie, 2000 (Box 54)
  - Queer Eye For The Straight Guy, 2004 (Box 54)
    Publicity still and clipping for television program.
  - Radio, 2003 (Box 54)
    Articles regarding gay radio station.
  - Reno 911!, 2003-2004 (Box 54)
  - Ring Of Fire - The Emile Griffith Story, 2005 Jan 16 (Box 54)
    Clipping re: documentary film.
  - Rocky Horror, ca. 2000 (Box 54)
    Playbill, slides, publicity stills, and photocopies of costume designs for production.
  - Ruthie & Connie: Every Room in the House, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Same Sex America, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Second Skin, 2000-2001 (Box 55)
  - Spaces / Free Expression, undated (Box 55)
    Guide to alternative and free exhibition space in New York City.
  - Speaking Of Charlie, 1988, 2004 (Box 54)
    Press re: play.
  - Splashlight Studios, undated (Box 55)